Claude Code is powerful out of the box...
But every session starts fresh.
It doesn't remember your team's rules.
Your project's architecture.
Or the mistakes it made yesterday...
ClaudeOS fixes that.
Four files load into every session...
automatically.
Your team's build commands and architecture.
Your personal review style and preferences.
Permission auto-approvals, so Claude
doesn't ask for confirmation on safe commands.
And a living memory... of patterns
learned across hundreds of sessions.
Plus twenty-two topic files,
auto-synced from Confluence every twenty-four hours.
Claude learns from its mistakes.
When it tries to use the gh CLI...
which isn't installed... that gets logged.
After multiple occurrences across sessions,
the pattern gets recognized...
and promoted to a permanent rule.
From that point on...
Claude never makes that mistake again.
The progression is... session log,
to recognized pattern, to permanent rule.
Five scheduled scripts
replace the manual loop.
Logging every hour. Distilling patterns daily.
Promoting rules weekly.
Syncing Confluence and Notion docs...
automatically.
All running on launchd, across two repos.
Ten agents total.
Custom slash commands turn
multi-step workflows... into one-liners.
Type slash review with a ticket number...
and Claude fetches the branch,
diffs every file, runs regression scans,
and posts a categorized review...
directly on the pull request.
Here's a real review it posted on Bitbucket.
Setting up a new repo...
takes one command.
Bootstrap copies your templates,
slash commands, automation scripts, and starter memory.
Checkpoint saves changes back.
Your conventions... travel with you...
across every project.
All of this... runs for about
four dollars a week.
Each script is budget-capped.
No surprises.