Claude Code is powerful out of the box.
But every session starts fresh.
It doesn't remember your team's rules,
your project's architecture,
or the mistakes it made yesterday.
ClaudeOS fixes that.
Four files load into every session automatically.
Your team's build commands and architecture.
Your personal review style and preferences.
Permission auto-approvals so Claude doesn't
ask for confirmation on safe commands.
And a living memory of patterns learned
across hundreds of sessions.
Plus 22 topic files,
auto-synced from Confluence every 24 hours.
Claude learns from its mistakes.
When it tries to use the gh CLI,
which isn't installed, that gets logged.
After multiple occurrences across sessions,
the pattern gets recognized
and promoted to a permanent rule.
From that point on,
Claude never makes that mistake again.
The progression is: session log,
to recognized pattern, to permanent rule.
Five scheduled scripts
replace the manual loop.
Logging every hour. Distilling patterns daily.
Promoting rules weekly.
Syncing Confluence and Notion docs automatically.
All running on launchd, across two repos.
Ten agents total.
Custom slash commands turn
multi-step workflows into one-liners.
Type slash review with a ticket number,
and Claude fetches the branch,
diffs every file, runs regression scans,
and posts a categorized review
directly on the pull request.
Here's a real review it posted on Bitbucket.
Setting up a new repo takes one command.
Bootstrap copies your templates,
slash commands, automation scripts,
and starter memory.
Checkpoint saves changes back.
Your conventions travel with you across every project.
The automation runs for about
four dollars a week.
Each script is budget-capped
so there are no surprises.